[Music]
as your business grows so does your
product catalog and before long
navigating through lengthy product lists
can consume your sellers valuable time
Microsoft co-pilot in Dynamics 365
business Central revolutionizes the
process of creating sales orders
invoices and quotes imagine you receive
an email from a customer with a list of
items they would like to purchase with
co-pilot you can simply copy the details
and paste them directly into business
Central co-pilot then ident identifies
the products in the email conversation
and uses the item details variants and
attributes in your catalog to suggest
matching products some orders are based
on what you've sold before so you can
also reference a previous order to have
co-pilot find those items for you or you
can describe the goods or services
needed with just a few words based on
your input co-pilot suggests line items
from your product catalog streamlining
the order taking process select the
suggested items finalize the order and
you're done it's that simple by
improving order entry co-pilot frees
time for sales teams to focus on
building relationships and delivering
exceptional customer experiences work
smarter not harder with co-pilot in
business Central